FIRST_NAME	LAST_NAME	AGE	NATIONALITY	POSITION	RNO	SQUAD	PREV_CLUB	DDATE	PROFILE_PIC	DESCRIPTION1	DESCRIPTION2	SPEED	STAMINA	PASSING	SHOOTING	DRIBBLING	HEADING
Wojciech	Szczesny	25	Poland	Goalkeeper	1	1	"Legia Warsaw, Brenford"	22-Sep-09	player_(1).jpg	"Wojciech continued to underline his status as one of Europe's top young goalkeepers with a fine 2013/14 campaign. The Pole's season began strongly with clean sheets in both legs of Arsenal's Champions League play off against Fenerbahce, plus the north London derby victory at home to Tottenham, where he made some crucial saves late on."	"More noteworthy performances included during the wins against Crystal Palace and Liverpool in late autumn as Arsenal ended 2014 at the summit of the Premier League.
Having kept a personal-best 16 clean sheets in the Premier League, Wojciech finished the season in style by sharing the Premier League’s ‘Golden Glove’ award with Chelsea’s Petr Cech.
A confident presence who communicates well, Wojciech joined the Arsenal Academy in 2006 from hometown club Legia Warsaw ? where he had made his first-team debut aged 15. He made his Arsenal bow in a Carling Cup win over West Bromwich Albion in 2009 and, after a successful loan at Brentford in 2009/10, debuted in the Premier League against Manchester United in December 2010. His Champions League debut came against Barcelona the following February.
Son of ex-Poland goalkeeper Maciej Szczesny, he is a regular for his country and won his first cap in November 2009."	87	90	67	88	87	77
David	Ospina	27	Colombia	Goalkeeper	2	13	"Atletico Nacional, Nice"	 	player_(24).jpg	Colombia international goalkeeper David Ospina signed for Arsenal from Nice in July 2014.	"Ospina began his career with Atletico Nacional, where he made 97 appearances before leaving to join Nice in 2008. He made 189 league appearances for Les Aiglons during his six-year spell with the French club.
The 6ft stopper had an impressive World Cup with Colombia, helping his country to the quarter-finals in Brazil with a series of fine displays.
Ospina made his first start for the national team in a 2010 World Cup qualifier against Bolivia, becoming the second youngest keeper to start for Colombia."	78	65	87	78	78	65
Mathieu	Debuchy	30	France	Defender	3	2	"Lille, Newcasle United"	 	player_(23).jpg	France international Mathieu Debuchy joined Arsenal in July 2014.	"The right back signed from Newcastle United after 18 months with the Magpies. Mathieu spent the first nine years of his senior career with French side Lille where he made 233 appearances in the league and a further 18 in the Champions League.
He helped the French side to a league and cup double in 2010/11 and was named in the Ligue 1 Team of the Season the following year.
He made his debut for France in October 2011 and featured in four of Les Bleus' five games at the 2014 World Cup.
"	88	74	78	88	88	61
Kieran	Gibbs	26	England	Defender	5	3	"Wimbledon, Norwich City "	31-Oct-07	player_(6).jpg	"Kieran enjoyed another impressive campaign and continued to produce assured performances as part of Arsenal's backline. He played 41 times, his best season in terms of appearances to date, and scored an important goal in the Champions League qualifier against Fenerbahce."	"His pace and composure on the ball made him a valuable outlet going forward, while the defensive side of his game continues to impress.
Kieran has been with the club since 2004, when he joined from the now-defunct Wimbledon Academy. He began as a winger, moving to left back after a successful loan spell with Norwich City in 2007/08 - the same season that saw him make his Arsenal debut.
He made his full England debut against Hungary in 2010 at the age of just 20, and earned a runners-up medal at the 2009 Uefa Under-21 Championship."	76	92	82	76	76	98
Gabriel	 	25	Brazil	Defender	7	5	"Vitoria, Villarreal"	 	player_(34).jpg	Brazilian defender Gabriel signed for Arsenal from Villarreal in January	"Primarily a centre back, 6ft 1in Gabriel began his career with Esporte Clube Vit?ria in Brazil, making his debut aged 19 before going on to feature more than 130 times for the Salvador club.The pacy defender, who can also play at left back or right back, joined Villarreal in 2013.
He was an ever-present in the side that conceded 17 goals in their first 19 La Liga matches and went 18 games unbeaten at the start of the 2014/15 season.
"	63	76	79	63	63	77
Laurent	Koscielny	30	France	Defender	8	6	"En Avant Guingamp,Tours,Lorient"	15-Aug-10	player_(10).jpg	Laurent cemented his position at the heart of Arsenal's defence alongside Per Mertesacker as their partnership received widespread praise during the 2013/14 season. The agile defender continued his habit of scoring in the big games when he turned in Arsenal's equaliser in the FA Cup final against Hull City.	"That moment was an impressive way to complete his fourth season in England. Laurent displayed his pace, awareness and tenacity throughout the campaign, making 46 appearances and scoring three goals. His consistency and ability to perform on the big occasions was recognised by the Arsenal fans when he was voted third in the Player of the Season poll.
Since joining from Lorient in 2010, he has established himself as one of the most highly-rated defenders in the Premier League, earning widespread plaudits for his displays. His fine form resulted in a first cap for France in November 2011, and he also appeared in Les Bleus’ Euro 2012 and World Cup 2014 campaigns. He is now a firm fixture at international level.
Previously, Laurent was with Ligue 2 side Tours. He then spent one season at Lorient before his move to north London."	78	79	63	78	78	87
Issac	Hayden	20	England	Defender	12	42	none	 	player_(29).jpg	"Defensive midfielder Isaac established himself as a senior member of the under-21 side in the 2013/14 campaign, captaining the team on a number of occasions"	"Defensive midfielder Isaac established himself as a senior member of the under-21 side in the 2013/14 campaign, captaining the team on a number of occasions.

The England youth international is comfortable on the ball, strong in the challenge and leads by example with his commitment and tenacity. 

Isaac made his debut for the first team in the Capital One Cup victory at West Bromwich Albion in September 2013, partnering Per Mertesacker in central defence. He made 15 appearances for the second string last season and three in the under-19s' Youth League campaign. 

The Essex-born youngster signed a new contract with the club in February 2014 and was named in the first team's Champions League squad last season."	85	88	74	63	82	92
Krystian	Buelik	17	England	Midfielder	23	36	Legia Warsaw	 	player_(33).jpg	Highly-rated Polish midfielder Krystian joined Arsenal from Legia Warsaw in January 2015.	"A defensive midfielder, the teenager, who has represented his country at youth level, made his senior debut in the Polish league aged just 16.
He made five appearances in the Ekstraklasa and one in the Europa League before making the move to north London."	82	90	89	71	85	76
Danny	Welbeck	25	England	Forward	27	23	"Manchester United, Preston (North End (loan), Sunderland (loan)"	 	player_(26).jpg	England international Danny joined Arsenal in September 2014.	"The 23-year-old joined from Manchester United, where he made a total of 142 appearances, scoring 29 goals.
Welbeck, who can play as a centre forward or a winger, developed through the youth ranks at Old Trafford and during his time there had successful loan spells at Preston North End and Sunderland.
Making his senior England debut in March 2011, Welbeck was in the England squads for both Euro 2012 and the 2014 World Cup."	78	71	97	79	89	63
Per	Mertesacker	31	Germany	Defender	6	4	"Werder Bremen, Hannover "	 	player_(11).jpg	"After a stellar campaign, Per finished second in the club's Player of the Season poll. The 6ft 6in defender's partnership with Laurent Koscielny continued to flourish and their understanding was evident in a number of clean-sheet victories throughout the year."	"Commanding in the air and adept on the ground, Per enjoyed a consistent campaign at the back, establishing himself as one of the key figures in the dressing room. He weighed in with a few important goals too, most notably his late equaliser against Wigan in the FA Cup semi-final.
Per had already enjoyed an impressive few seasons at Emirates Stadium after joining from Werder Bremen in August 2011. An important member of the German national squad since 2004, he started out at Hannover 96 before moving to Bremen in 2006, having shone at that year’s World Cup.
He made almost 200 appearances in five years there, while winning a runners-up medal at Euro 2008 and featuring in the 2010 World Cup squad. He has also travelled to Euro 2012 and the 2014 World Cup, and has reached a century of caps for the ‘Nationalmannschaft’, having represented his country numerous times at youth level.
"	79	82	76	79	79	92
Nacho	Monreal	29	Spain	Defender	9	18	"Osasuna, Malaga"	02-Feb-13	player_(13).jpg	"Nacho completed another solid season at the club, making 36 appearances for the Gunners. The Spaniard provided stiff competition for Kieran Gibbs at left back, proving to be a reliable option for Arsene Wenger."	"He has adapted smoothly to the rigours of the Premier League and made an impact with his clever positioning, fine technique and vital interceptions. His ability to combine well with players further forward makes him a useful attacking outlet.
A highlight of Nacho's season was scoring the decisive penalty in the Capital One Cup penalty shoot-out win over West Bromwich Albion and he also played a full part in the FA Cup victories against Tottenham and Liverpool.
Nacho (full name Ignacio Monreal Eraso) arrived from Malaga, for whom he had featured in the 2012/13 Champions League. He had helped them to fourth place in La Liga the previous season, his first with the Andalusian club. Before that, he represented hometown side Osasuna, for whom he made 127 appearances - helping them to a Europa League semi-final in 2006/07.
Previously a regular in Spain’s Under-21 side, he made his full debut against Macedonia in August 2009 and now battles with Barcelona’s Jordi Alba for the left-back spot."	63	63	78	63	87	89
Calum	Chambers	20	England	Defender	10	21	Southampton	 	player_(25).jpg	Highly-rated defender Calum Chambers signed for Arsenal from Southampton in July 2014.	"The England youth international graduated from the Saints' academy system to make his senior debut in August 2012. He made his first-team league debut on the opening day of the 2013/14 season, when he played the full 90 minutes at right back in a 1?0 win against West Bromwich Albion. He went on to make 22 appearances for the south coast club.
Tall and athletic, the versatile youngster started his career in midfield, but established himself at right back last season and can also play in the centre of defence. He is currently captain of England Under-19s and has also represented his country at under-17 level.
"	89	78	63	89	78	88
Hector	Bellerin	20	Spain	Defender	11	39	Watford	 	player_(28).jpg	Pacy right back Hector was promoted to Arsenal's first team at the start of the 2014/15 campaign after he spent time on loan at Watford the previous season to gain valuable experience.	"The young Spaniard also featured in the majority of Arsenal's 2013/14 Youth League campaign and made seven appearances for the under-21s, scoring two goals. 

The energetic defender made his debut for the senior side in September 2013 when he came on as a late substitute against West Brom in the League Cup. 

Strong in possession and direct going forward, Hector was part of the squad that visited New York in pre-season and he also featured in the 2014 Emirates Cup where he produced an eye-catching display against Benfica.

He then made his full debut against Borussia Dortmund the following month before making his first Premier League appearance when he started against Hull City in October.
Hector impressed so much that he quickly became a regular in Arsene Wenger's matchday squad for 2014/15 as back-up to Mathieu Debuchy and Calum Chambers at right back."	74	78	89	79	88	92
Tomas	Rosicky	35	Czech	Midfielder	4	7	"Borussia Dortmund, Sparta Prague, CKD Kompresory"	09-Aug-06	player_(18).jpg	"Tomas's 2013/14 season will be remembered for three outstanding goals that outlined his technical prowess and ability to influence the big games. The Czech international also experienced his most successful season at the club in terms of appearances, featuring 39 times in all competitions."	"The midfielder's first goal of the season came in the FA Cup third-round tie against Tottenham. After dispossessing Danny Rose on the halfway line he raced through on goal before sending a deft chip over Hugo Lloris. Rosicky also caught the eye when he rounded off a fine team move with a cool finish against Sunderland - but his best goal was in another north London derby, this time at White Hart Lane when he found the top corner with a stunning first-time strike.
Known as one of Europe’s most gifted and exciting attacking midfielders for more than a decade, Tomas joined Arsenal from Borussia Dortmund in the summer of 2006, having won the Bundesliga and been a Uefa Cup finalist after arriving from Sparta Prague. He won two titles in the Czech Republic and was twice named Czech Player of the Year (in 2002 and 2006).
He captained his national side at Euro 2012 before suffering an achilles injury."	82	52	88	82	82	78
Mikel	Arteta	33	Spain	Midfielder	13	8	"Everton, Real Sociedad, Rangers, Barcelona"	 	player_(2).jpg	Mikel was promoted to club captain at the start of the 2014/15 season.	"Generally sitting as the deepest of Arsenal’s three central midfielders, he demonstrated his experience and class throughout, providing an effective shield for the back four while instigating numerous forward moves with his fine technique and passing ability.
A highly-consistent player who is a big influence on and off the pitch, Mikel captained the side for much of the season and led by example with a string of classy performances.
Arteta's three goals during the season all came from the penalty spot. In the FA Cup quarter-final against Everton he was made to re-take a spot kick but held his nerve to give Arsenal a crucial lead in the tie.
Mikel has been one of the Premier League’s leading lights in his position for almost a decade, having represented Everton with distinction for six-and-a-half years before joining the Gunners in August 2011. He made 209 appearances for the Goodison Park side, scored 35 times and was named their Player of the Year on three occasions.
He began his career at Barcelona, with a spell at Paris St-Germain providing his introduction to senior football before moves to Rangers - where he won all three major domestic Scottish trophies - and Real Sociedad.
Although capped at youth level for Spain, he is yet to receive a full call-up for his country."	88	82	85	78	76	91
Olivier	Giroud	29	France	Forward	24	12	"Grenoble, Istres (loan), Tours, Montpellier"	 	player_(7).jpg	"Olivier produced another impressive campaign and scored 22 goals, five more than his first season with the club. After a strong pre-season, he scored in each of the Gunners' opening four league games. He also netted crucial strikes away at Newcastle and Aston Villa during a busy festive period and contributed to Arsenal's run to the FA Cup final with goals in the victories over Coventry City and Everton."	"Olivier displayed his technical prowess when he scored a sublime goal against West Ham United, taking down a long ball in the six-yard box with a deft touch before finding the net with a low drive.
One of the most talented strikers to have emerged from France in recent years, Olivier joined Arsenal in July 2012 from then-Ligue 1 champions Montpellier, for whom he had top-scored in their ‘double’ win the previous season. Prior to that, he represented Tours - playing with Laurent Koscielny - and was named Ligue 2 Player of the Year for 2009/10.
Olivier has become an important member of the France squad. He debuted in November 2011 and played in Euro 2012 and was a member of Les Blues’ squad at the 2014 World Cup.
"	76	87	74	70	88	79
Theo	Walcott	26	England	Forward	25	14	Southampton	19-Aug-06	player_(20).jpg	"Theo's 2013/14 campaign was marred by injury, restricting him to just 18 appearances. The forward began the season well, setting up Olivier Giroud's winner against Tottenham and scoring a sumptuous volley in the 2-1 win against Marseille."	"An abdominal problem kept him out until the middle of November but he didn't take long to rediscover his form in front of goal, scoring four times in December. However, Theo's season came to an abrupt end when he sustained a cruciate knee ligament injury in the FA Cup third-round win against Tottenham at the turn of the year.
Theo joined from Southampton in 2006 at the age of just 16, winning a call-up to England’s World Cup squad that summer. He became the country’s youngest-ever full international later that year when he faced Hungary aged 17 years and 75 days, and has been a mainstay in the national squad ever since. In 2008 he scored a memorable hat-trick away to Croatia in a World Cup qualifier.
Renowned for his pace and movement, Theo is also the youngest-ever goalscorer for England Under-21s, and was a runner up at the 2009 European Under-21 Championship."	79	89	85	89	90	63
Alexis	 	27	Chile	Forward	26	17	"Cobreloa, Colo-Colo, River Plate, Udinese, Barcelona"	 	player_(22).jpg	Chile international striker Alexis joined Arsenal in July 2014.	"The exciting forward signed from Barcelona, where he made a total of 88 appearances and scored 39 goals during his three seasons with the Catalan side.
With Barcelona, Sanchez won both La Liga (2012/13) and the Copa del Rey (2012), as well as the Spanish Super Cup on two occasions (2011, 2013), the Uefa Super Cup (2011) and the Fifa Club World Cup (2011).
Regarded as one of the world’s finest talents, Sanchez played a starring role at the 2014 World Cup in Brazil, where Chile qualifyied from their group (which included the Netherlands, Spain and Australia) and reaching the round of 16. During the tournament, Sanchez scored two goals from his four appearances.
The striker started his career with Cobreloa, based in Calama in north Chile, where he spent a season before moving to Santiago-based Colo-Colo, where he won the Chilean Primera Division in 2007.
After convincing performances in Chile between 2005 and 2007, Sanchez went on loan to Argentine side River Plate, where he added the Argentinian Primera Division to his honours.
Following his success in South America, Sanchez made a permanent move to Serie A side Udinese in 2008, where he spent three seasons, scoring 20 goals from 95 appearances, before making the move to Barcelona in 2011.
"	63	81	88	64	87	78
Serge	Gnabry	20	Germany	Forward	28	27	VfB Stuttgart	26-Sep-12	player_(8).jpg	"After making an impressive start to the season with the youth teams, Serge was quickly called up to the first-team squad and scored his first goal for the club in the Premier League game against Swansea City. The talented forward went on to start eight games for the Gunners and signed a new long-term contract with the club in October 2013."	"He continued to compete for a starting berth during the winter months and received widespread praise for his fearless display against Tottenham in the third round of the FA Cup. The young German netted six goals for the academy sides, of which four of those came in the Uefa Youth League campaign which saw the young Gunners reach the last eight.
Serge, who is equally at home anywhere across the front line, made his full debut in the memorable 7-5 League Cup victory away at Reading in 2012.
Having signed his first professional contract with the club in the summer of 2012, the following year he was part of the first team’s tour to Asia, and featured heavily in Indonesia, Vietnam and Japan. He also played in the Emirates Cup against Napoli.
Serge has also made an impact at international level, featuring frequently for the German youth sides from under-16 to under-19 levels. He scored two fine goals for the under-18s against France in March 2013.
"	63	70	58	68	81	89
Jack	Wilshere	23	Egland	Midfielder	14	10	Bolton (loan)	13-Sep-08	player_(21).jpg	"Jack produced a host of impressive performances last season before suffering an ankle injury on international duty in March, which kept him out until the final two games of the campaign. Playing in his preferred position as a central midfielder, Jack showed a marked improvement in front of goal with five goals, including an outstanding team strike against Norwich City that was voted Goal of the Season. Another high point was his brace in Arsenal's 2-0 win at home to Marseille in the Champions League."	"One of the most exciting English talents of his generation, he has been with Arsenal since the age of nine and won the FA Youth Cup in 2009. After a loan spell with Bolton in 2009/10 he returned to the club and was named the PFA Young Player of the Season in 2010/11. He holds the distinction of being the Gunners’ youngest-ever league player (16 years 256 days) and the youngest to represent Arsenal in Europe (16 years 329 days).
An important member of the England national team since 2010, he signed a new long-term contract with Arsenal in December 2012.
"	90	76	88	63	79	77
Mesut	Ozil	27	Germany	Midfielder	15	11	"Schalke, Werder Bremen, Real Madrid"	 	player_(15).jpg	"Mesut made an immediate impression in English football with a string of sparkling performances during his first season with the club. After becoming the club's record signing, he set up Olivier Giroud on his debut at Sunderland before scoring a sublime goal in the 2-0 win against Napoli. He went on to register a brace against Norwich City, plus further strikes at home to Hull and Everton before the turn of the year."	"The Germany international suffered a hamstring injury against Bayern Munich in March, which kept him out for more than a month. But he made a positive impact on his return, scoring and setting up another in the 3-0 win against Newcastle.
Widely regarded as one of the world’s finest midfielders, Ozil spent three years at Real Madrid, making 159 appearances and scoring 27 goals. While at the Bernabeu, he won the league title in 2012 and was a runner-up twice - also picking up a Copa del Rey winner’s medal in 2011.
A creative force blessed with good acceleration and an eye for a killer pass, Mesut has made more assists than any other player in Europe’s top five leagues during the last half-decade.
A full Germany international with a scoring record of almost one in three, he made his debut, aged 20, against Norway in 2009. Mesut, who is of Turkish descent, then starred at the 2010 World Cup and was among the nominees for the Golden Ball award. Two years later he was named in the Euro 2012 Team of the Tournament, after helping Germany to the semi finals. He also was a member of Germany’s squad at the 2014 World Cup.
"	87	79	94	89	91	87
Alex	Chamberlain	22	England	Midfielder	16	15	Southampton	 	player_(14).jpg	"Alex's season got off to a frustrating start when he sustained a knee injury in the opening Premier League game at home to Aston Villa, which kept him out for the remainder of 2013. He returned to the side in early January and his energy and direct style of play had a positive impact."	"The versatile midfielder scored a second-half brace against Crystal Palace at the beginning of February and put in a man-of-the-match display in the FA Cup fifth-round victory over Liverpool, scoring one and setting up another.
However, his stand-out performance came in the 1-1 draw against Bayern Munich in the Allianz Arena. Playing in central midfield, his ability to take on defenders, change the pace of the game and make incisive passes earned widespread praise and enhanced his reputation as a star in the making.
A groin injury kept Alex out of the final games of the season - including the FA Cup final - but he managed to prove his fitness in time to make England's 2014 World Cup squad.
Capable of altering the tempo of a game with a driving run or piece of skill, Alex joined the Gunners in August 2011 and burst on to the scene five months later with a man-of-the-match performance against Manchester United.
His fine first season saw him promoted to the England senior set-up and he played three times at Euro 2012. His excellent start to international life continued in 2013 when he scored a superb goal against Brazil at the Maracana Stadium.
Son of ex-England star Mark Chamberlain, Alex joined the club from Southampton, where he had become their second-youngest player - behind Theo Walcott - in 2009/10 and was prominent in their promotion from League One the following season.
"	89	63	87	74	78	79
Aaron	Ramsey	25	Wales	Midfielder	17	16	" Nottingham Forest (loan), Cardiff City"	13-Aug-08	player_(7).jpg	"Last term will live long in the memory of Player of the Season Aaron Ramsey. The Welshman scored 16 goals in 34 appearances, including a dramatic winner in the FA Cup final to seal a stunning personal campaign."	"After an impressive pre-season, Aaron got off to a flyer with eight goals in his first nine games as Arsenal quickly moved to the summit of the Premier League. Crucial goals against Liverpool and Borussia Dortmund followed and the Welshman also netted a brace against former club Cardiff City at the end of November. A thigh injury suffered on Boxing Day kept him out for just under four months but his spell on the sidelines had no bearing on his outstanding form.
The midfielder netted a further three goals after his return to take his tally to 16 for the season, which ended with a richly-deserved FA Cup winner’s medal.
Aaron joined the Gunners from Cardiff City in the summer of 2008, aged just 17. He had already become the Bluebirds’ youngest player (at 16 years 124 days), and was the fifth-youngest scorer in Champions League history when he netted for Arsenal against Fenerbahce in October of that year.
His progress received a setback when he sustained a serious leg fracture in February 2010, necessitating a long road to recovery that took in loans at Nottingham Forest and back at Cardiff. His rehabilitation was successful, and he is now a key player for club and country.
He has captained Wales, and represented Team GB in the 2012 Olympics - scoring as they reached the quarter-finals."	81	78	89	85	63	98
Santi	Cazorla	31	Spain	Midfielder	18	19	"Malaga, Villarreal, Recreativo, Villarreal, Oviedo"	 	player_(3).jpg	"Santi continued to impress during his second campaign at Arsenal. Despite some early-season injury problems, the Spaniard was a mainstay in the team, starting 41 games and scoring seven goals. He showed his versatility by regularly interchanging positions across Arsenal's midfield and attack, while combining well with Aaron Ramsey and Mesut Ozil."	"Santi opened his account for the season with an excellent strike against Liverpool before scoring four goals in January. He produced his best moment in an Arsenal shirt in the FA Cup final against Hull City with a stunning free-kick to haul the Gunners back into the game.
Signed from Malaga in August 2012, the technically-gifted playmaker slotted seamlessly into Premier League life - and proceeded to play more games than any other squad member during the 2013/13 campaign, including all 38 league matches.
Before joining Malaga in 2011, Santi spent two successful spells at Villarreal, making 181 appearances and helping them to second place in La Liga in 2008. In between those two spells he was named Spanish Player of the Year in 2007 while with Recreativo de Huelva.
He is a regular in the Spain set-up and was a member of their victorious Euro 2008 and Euro 2012 squads. He also featured in Spain’s run to the 2013 Confederations Cup final and was named in their squad for the 2014 World Cup.
"	71	63	81	88	89	87
Mathieu	Flamini	31	England	Midfielder	19	20	"Marseille, Arsenal, AC Milan"	 	player_(5).jpg	"Mathieu proved to be a valuable addition to the squad after rejoining the club in August 2013. He made an immediate impact on his second debut when he came on as a first-half substitute in the north London derby against Tottenham and produced a battling display at the heart of the midfield. His strength in the challenge, composure on the ball and organisational skills were immediately highly-valued by the team and his manager."	"He made 36 appearances last season and netted two goals, including an important equaliser at home to Manchester City.
Mathieu first joined Arsenal in 2004 from Ligue 1 side Marseille and made 153 appearances for the Gunners before joining AC Milan in the summer of 2008. His stand-out season came in 2007/08, when he was a fixture in the midfield and delivered a string of all-action performances - catching the eye in a team that challenged for the Premier League title.
Mathieu won the Serie A title with Milan in 2010/11, playing an important role in the middle of the park. After his contract expired at the San Siro, he began training with Arsenal - signing for the club two weeks into the 2013/14 Premier League season.
"	70	89	71	90	78	87
Abou	Diaby	29	France	Midfielder	20	24	"Auxerre, Paris Saint-Germain"	21-Jan-06	player_(4).jpg	Abou made his long-awaited return to the first team in the last Premier League game of the 2013/14 season away to Norwich City after more than 14 months out with a cruciate knee ligament injury. The midfielder spent much of his rehabilitation in his native France before returning to training in spring and making an appearance for the under-21 side in April.	"When fully fit, there are few Premier League midfielders who can match Abou for technique and presence on the ball. He demonstrated this with four fine performances early in the 2012/13 season, particularly during a 2-0 win at Liverpool.
He joined the Gunners from Auxerre at the age of 19 and, despite some serious injuries, has been integral to Arsene Wenger’s plans when fit. The same can be said with the French national team, for whom he has won 16 caps and featured heavily in the 2010 World Cup campaign, playing all 270 minutes. He also won the Uefa Under-19 Championship in 2005 before injuries cruelly interrupted his career.
This season Abou will be hoping that, after completing his recovery, he is afforded the lengthy run of fitness that he deserves."	87	74	70	87	63	78
Francis	Conquelin	24	France	Midfielder	21	34	"Freiberg (loan), Lorient (loan)"	23-Sep-08	player_(30).jpg	Young French midfielder Francis Coquelin featured for Arsenal across all competitions last season.	"A tigerish defensive midfielder with good acceleration and composure on the ball, his promising progress continued as he passed the 40-appearance mark for the Gunners. Starting all three Capital One Cup games, he also enjoyed a fine 90 minutes in the FA Cup win over Swansea and impressed in the Champions League group stage victory against Olympiacos. In addition he made three Premier League starts.
Francis also went on a one-month loan spell to Charlton Athletic at the start of the 2014/15 season and returned to Arsenal with valuable first-team experience, slotting straight back into Arsene Wenger's team.
Well known for his versatility, having also played in both full-back positions, Francis arrived from Laval in 2008 and was an FA Youth Cup winner in his first season as an Arsenal player. He debuted for the first team in the 6-0 Carling Cup win over Sheffield United in September 2008. He enjoyed a highly productive season on loan with French Ligue 1 side Lorient in 2010/11, with his achievements including a dramatic goal in the local derby against Rennes.
Francis has represented his country throughout the youth levels, and was a UEFA Under-19 Championship winner in 2010 ? starting four of France’s five games. He also competed in the FIFA Under-20 World Cup in 2011.
"	78	85	78	89	89	88
Gedion	Zelalem	18	Germany	Midfielder	22	35	Hertha Berlin	 	player_(31).jpg	Exciting prospect Gedion became the first player to feature for Arsenal who was born after Arsene Wenger took charge when he made his debut in the FA Cup fourth-round game against Coventry City. The Germany youth international spent the majority of his season with the under-21s and played 22 times for the academy sides.	"Gedion arrived at the club in January 2013 after he was spotted by scout and former Gunner Danny Karbassiyoon playing in the Dallas Cup.
Formerly of Hertha Berlin, Gedion broke into the Gunners’ under-21 team at the end of the 2012/13 season, turning in an assured performance on his debut against Liverpool at Anfield in April and winning many admirers with his ability on the ball and willingness to adapt to the physical side of English football.
Imaginative in possession and blessed with clever movement, the youngster added to that appearance with three more before the end of the campaign. During the summer of 2013 his progress continued when he was named in the first-team squad for the Asia Tour, and played in all four of the side’s games in Indonesia, Vietnam and Japan.
Gedion particularly impressed with his vision - his assist for Theo Walcott’s goal against Nagoya Grampus was especially memorable.
He also featured against Galatasaray in the Emirates Cup, and was subsequently named in the first-team squad for 2013/14, despite technically still being a first-year scholar in the academy.
"	88	88	63	81	74	82
